# Ndigwe Chinenye Precious

**CONTACT** No 1 super master close

E-mail: pndigwe23@gmail.com Amuwo odofin **Website:** <a href="https://ndigwe-chinenye.netlify.app">https://ndigwe-chinenye.netlify.app</a> **Phone:** 08106500629 Lagos State

**PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY** 

Experienced IT personnel committed to maintaining cutting-edge technical skills and upto-date industry knowledge.

Strategic Marketing and Communications Consultant with a firm grasp of corporate messaging and branding. Exceptional leader talented at big data analysis, customer support, quality control, task management and Technically-savvy.

Flexible and hardworking in deadline-driven environments.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Responsive Design
- Superior verbal and written communication skills
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- Exceptional attention to detail
- Database Management
- Time management
- Creative and innovative

# WORK **EXPERIENCE**

### GoodMan Training Institute

June 2013 — April 2014

Computer Basic/ Web Design Tutor

- Training students on the basis of using the computer and introduction to front-end web design.
- Created curriculum and planned course content and methods of instruction.
- Increased enrollment by 20% in Adult Continuing education and Enrichment programs by offering new and innovative programming.
- Wrote and designed continuing education examinations.
- Instructed students on a variety of skills, including web design, creativity e.t.c.
- Developed detailed daily lesson plans for activities.

## Mayakorp Nigeria

May 2017 — Nov 2017

Technical / IT Support Intern

- Evaluated potential software products based on new and existing system development and migration requirements.
- Upgraded and expanded network systems and their components.
- Documented all server and network problems and other unusual events in detail.
- Incorporated feedback and recommendations from other staff members when modifying the software.
- Performed initial client assessment and analysis to begin the research process.
- Advocated for end-users to perform testing and problem analysis for the server, desktop and IT infrastructure work.

#### **JustFantastic**

Jun 2017 — August 2020

Online Shop/ Catalog Manager

- Online Shop/ Catalogue Manager editing product images/uploads on the e-commerce
- Content writing/management for individual products, product Search engine optimization, and vendor registration.
- Managed creative projects from concept to completion while managing outside vendors.

- Communicated with vendors regarding back order availability, future inventory and special orders.
- Contacted customer to follow up on purchases, suggest new merchandise, and inform them about promotions and upcoming events.

#### Bring It On Africa

May 2018 — September 2019.

Technical / IT Support / Project Manager

- Oversaw multiple projects across all phases of development.
- Monitored workflow and make timeline adjustments as needed.
- Worked as part of an interdisciplinary team to achieve project milestones.
- Collaborated with development to plan project sprints.
- Developed status reports, cost estimates, and resource plans.
- Make vital decisions and drive decision-making across projects.
- Implemented and maintained development best practices.
- Managed resource and capacity planning for projects.

EDUCATION BSc in Computer Science

November 2014 — August 2018

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

SSCE / WASCE

February 2012 — August 2013

Christ The King Catholic College

QUALIFICATIONS

- Kaspersky Endpoint Security Associate
- Kaspersky Endpoint Security and Management Small Business Certification
- Google Digital Garage Online Marketing Fundamentals Qualification
- NetApp Virtualization Technology Fundamentals Certification

REFERENCES

Prince Henry Ikechukwu Ndigwe. Email: ndigwehenry@gmail.com

Phone: 08066425357

Ndigwe Chinenye Precious 2